devinere.com.au 2008-07-18

# Devine Real Estate

**PRIVACY ACT 1988**

General Notice

Strathfield Real Estate (Mgmt) Pty Ltd trading as Devine Real Estate respects your right to privacy. We are bound by the National Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act 1988. Those Principles regulate most of our activities with respect to personal information collected, stored, used and disclosed by us. However, the activities of all organizations directly relating to personal information of current or former employees contained in employee records are not covered by the Principles.

Vendor/Prospective Vendors & Purchasers/Prospective Purchasers

In our agency business we use personal information collected from vendors and prospective vendors to perform our obligations under our agreement with vendors, or to provide market appraisals to prospective vendors.

We use personal information collected from purchasers and prospective purchasers to inform them of properties for sale. Personal information may also be collected during an open house inspection for security purposes and we may contact the prospective purchaser with respect to that property and other properties which we believe may interest the prospective purchaser.

We may use the information for direct marketing purposes and to seek potential clients through the promotional activities of the agent. In providing the information the parties agree to this use unless they advise us differently.

We may disclose information to other parties including to potential purchasers or vendors, or to media organizations, on the internet, or to clients of the agent both existing and potential, as well as to parties engaged to evaluate the property, for example pest and building inspectors, etc., and to owners' corporations, government and statutory bodies, financial institutions, valuers and to third parties as required by law.

Landlords/Prospective Landlords

We use personal information collected from landlords and prospective landlords to act as the landlord's agent and to perform our obligations under our agreements with landlords, or to provide market appraisals to prospective landlords.

We may also use that information for direct marketing purposes and to seek potential clients through the promotional activities of the agent. In providing the information the parties agree to this use unless they advise us differently.

We may disclose information to other parties including to potential tenants, media organizations, on the internet, or to clients of the agent both existing and potential, as well as to tradespeople, owners' corporations, government and statutory bodies, financial institutions and to third parties as required by law.

Tenants/Prospective Tenants

Personal information is collected from tenants or potential tenants in the course of a tenancy application and any subsequent tenancy as is necessary for the agent to verify the potential tenant's identity, to process and evaluate the application and to manage the tenancy.

Personal information collected in the application and during the course of the tenancy, including through property inspection reports, may be disclosed to other parties including to the landlord, employment and personal referees, as well as to tradespeople, owners' corporations, government and statutory authorities, financial institutions and other agents and operators of tenancy reference databases and to third parties as required by law. Information already held on tenancy reference databases may also be disclosed to us. If the tenant fails to comply with their obligations under the tenancy agreement, that fact may also be disclosed to the landlord, other agents and operators of tenancy reference databases. If this information is not provided, we may not be able to process the application and manage the tenancy.

General

We will only disclose the above-mentioned information to other parties as required to perform our duties under any agreement, to achieve the purposes specified above and to provide an effective service, or as otherwise allowed under the Privacy Act 1988.

Real estate and tax laws require some of the above-mentioned information to be collected. If the information is not provided, we may not be able to act effectively or at all.

If you would like to access this information you can do so by contacting us on 9747 1144.
